[Music]
Okay, girls. What do we rank
Thunderlane?
>> He looks like the type who doesn't wipe
his ass and then he asks you to shake
his hand.
>> OMG, Fluttershy, you can't say that.
>> His mohawk is kind of cool. Mohawks are
rock and roll.
>> I give him a 2 out of 10. I would rank
him higher if he wasn't. Well, Black,
>> how many attack points does he have?
>> You're playing the game wrong, Pinky.
This isn't Pokémon. We're ranking boys
on attractiveness.
>> I don't want to objectify ponies.
>> You're being mentally challenged again.
Stallions only make up 2% of the My
Little Pony population. They're
basically not even people.
>> Well, then I'm done playing. I don't
want to be a part of your group sexism.
>> You are dressed like an actual baby, so
it's no surprise that you're acting like
a big one right now. What do we think
about Doctor Who? Nah,
>> he looks like he has at least three
little boys trapped in his basement.
>> Okay, well, Fluttershy, you are savage
tonight.
>> They don't call me Fluttershits for
nothing.
>> What the actual hell? All over my new
window. Are you dead ass? Clean it up.
>> No ponytails, Fluttershit. What to do?
>> Fluttershy, stop. We're playing a game
and you're just being a bully to
Twilight.
>> It's Fluttershit tonight, not
Fluttershy.
>> You see the distance between these two
cups? I am this close away from punching
you.
>> Try it and see what happens.
>> Oh,
>> let's continue the game.
>> I don't know. Maybe we should play
something else if it's going to get this
heated.
>> We're not playing something else. I want
to continue being sexist.
>> Yeah, no, we're playing Candyland with
that attitude.
>> Hold still. I'll try to
>> I got you, girl. We can fix this the
same way we fix things on the farm with
some good old duct tape.
>> What in Celestia's name are you doing?
>> Oh, I misread the situation. I thought
we were going to take her out back to
shoot her. Hey, what stallion are we
going to objectify next?
>> Next on the list, we have
>> He looks like the type who's packing a
whole entire dynamite stick in his
pants.
Apple bottom. What the hell? You can't
just say that.
>> What can I say, girls? I would know.
>> I told you you couldn't sneak in a
picture of care package just to see what
we'd say. Boyfriends are off the list.
>> I had to do it just once since he won't
be my boyfriend for very much longer.
>> No flipping way. You're finally going to
propose to him like we've been saying.
>> I already did. We're engaged now. Still
haven't picked a date for the wedding,
though.
>> When's the wedding? Are we invited? You
know, I'm super homophobic, but you're
black, and being both black and gay
means the world is like two times as
hard on you than it is on others. And
the fact that you haven't off yourself
already, I can respect that.
>> Thanks, Rainbow Dash. Very cool.
>> Hey, did you know that some say that
even though I'm blue on the outside and
black on the inside? I say the N word
all the time. I'll even say it right
now.
>> Hold up. Who the hell is this Apple
Bottom [__]
>> Apple Bottom is my cousin.
>> And you invited him and he's gay, but
you know I'm homophobic. This is my
slumber party, Fluttershy. I'm the host.
I decide who is allowed. Apple Bottom is
our new gay friend. Every girl group
needs one of those. And Applejack's
brother, Big Mac, is always too busy to
hang out with us.
>> So, you picked this thing up off the
street like a dog.
>> More like a stray cat since we just made
some friendly noises and left a trail of
a crushed up granola bar.
>> Being gay is illegal in Ponyville. I'll
remind you, if the cops find us housing
a homosexual, we are all being sent to
the Ponyville gas chambers. Fluttershy
were always housing. One Rainbow Dash is
a whole ass lesbian.
>> She's what?
>> Hey, you know what would be super fun?
Gay boy. Since it's August, the spirit
Halloween down the street just opened
its doors. And you always say your
boyfriend is into some dark twisted
[__] What do you say you call him up
and suggest throwing your wedding there
before the grand opening this weekend?
>> What if he's busy?
>> Then it'll be even funnier.
>> You can't do that. Celestia strictly
forbids homosexuality.
And there is no holier union than that
of a stallion and a marin marriage.
>> Celestia is away on a business trip
anyway and won't be back until next
week. She'll never know. I'm so nervous.
>> He's not even your boyfriend. Why are
you the one nervous?
[Music]
>> What do you want? I'm busy.
>> Cheese and crackers. He answered. Apple
bottom say something.
>> Uh, hey Gary package. What are you
doing?
>> I'm working.
He works as a male pony. I'm more
attracted to a pony's heart than how
much is written on their bank statements
every month.
>> Who are you talking to? Do I hear others
on the line?
>> He's on to us.
>> Oh, it's it's nothing the TV is on. I
wanted to ask you something.
>> Make it fast. I have somewhere I have to
be in 5.
>> Say it, [__] It's now or never.
>> I was wondering if you maybe want to get
married tomorrow at 5 in the afternoon
at Spirit Halloween. I know this is a
bit sudden and unnull.
>> Is he still there?
>> I suppose I can take some time off of
work so we can do that love.
>> He did it. I told you he was going to
say yes. He loves your ass.
>> No pony even cares. That's so ginger to
get up right now. Literally what? Lol.
Who even are you?
[Music]
Princess Celestia, I will do the job
that your cowardly [__] made apprentice
is too scared to do. I will uphold your
laws while you're away and keep the
disease that is being gay off these
streets covered in horseshit.
[Music]
>> No pony saw you come in.
>> No, no pony saws. Here's the wedding
cake sampler. Five flavors, 5 minutes.
Choose which one you like best, then
yeet yourself out of sugar cube corner.
Being that Ponyville is one of the most
homophobic places in Equestria, I'm
putting my life on the line just by
supporting you. You know, if Princess
Celestia finds out, I will be strung up
in the streets and pelted with rocks.
So, I'd better get compensation out of
this.
Pinkie Pie, I'm done putting the price
stickers on the prepackaged cookies.
>> You still didn't do the south end of the
store. Do better.
>> Is the lemon good?
>> I'm going to try the red velvet cake.
No, I was going to try that one next.
[Applause]
>> Don't forget to try the cherry with dark
chocolate chunks.
>> Oh, I would never. I would never.
>> Which is your favorite so far?
>> Well, I don't know. I haven't tried any
yet. What do you like?
>> It's hard to decide. I don't really like
cake.
>> Rainbow Dash. Look, it's Sauron. One of
the Wonderbolts.
>> So,
>> so I'm going to be a Wonderbolt someday,
too.
>> Um, no you won't, [__] We've been
through this. You're disabled. You will
never fly. You are useless and will
amount to nothing. What are you two
doing in Pinkie Pie's bakery?
>> Nothing. What about you?
>> I was given Scootaloo for the day
because her aunts want a day to
themselves because Scootaloo is annoying
as [__] But because she's annoying as
[__] I don't want to watch her either.
So, I want to pass her off to Pinkie
Pie.
>> That's so sad.
>> So, I heard you're getting married. I'll
say it takes a massive pair of balls to
really try throwing a gay wedding while
Princess Celestia is out of town. We
wanted to get married here specifically
because it would be a form of protest.
We want to show all ponies, even here in
Ponyville, that all ponies have the
right to be whoever they want to be.
We're going to hold the ceremony in the
back of Spirit Halloween.
>> Okay. Damn you, too, huh? Then you're
like, Mega Screwed when she comes back.
Cause Spirit Halloween is Celestia's
favorite store.
>> What do you mean you two?
>> Isn't your cousin Apple Bottom and Care
Package getting married there, too? Same
time, same place.
Oh my god. Oh my god. I am so sorry. I
didn't mean to do that. Ah crap. No. No.
No. My car is ruined. Oh my Gaga. I ran
over Dr. Hooves. How am I supposed to
keep my job as an Uber driver now? I'm
going to get fired. I am in so much
trouble.
>> Will you be coming to Saurin and Brin's
gay wedding? King, Sombra.
>> A gay wedding? No. No. I only date
straight guys to feel something. And you
can can't find any at one of those.
>> That doesn't sound very healthy.
>> Hey, I I just said to feel something. I
never said if those feelings were
positive or negative.
>> So, is Pinkie Pie here?
>> Pinkie Pie is not here.
>> Why is she hiding from me? Is it because
I didn't wipe my ass?
>> It's not you, Dashy. I just don't want
to be seen supporting the homosexual
lifestyle.
>> Checks out. Hey, can you tell Applejack
to be careful? I heard Fluttershy wants
to kill her. I thought I'd let you know
since you're her family.
>> OMG, are you dead ass babes? You know,
the quiet ones are always the most
unhinged little [__] Like,
respectfully, but also not.
>> Who's Fluttershy?
>> Some pony in my friend group of six bad
[__] we call the main six. I often
forget about her though. But I
remembered she existed when I overheard
her telling Lyra and Bon Bon that she
wants to shoot Applejack with a gun.
Lyra and Bon Bon are also going through
relationship problems. I saw one of them
punch the other.
care package. I need to talk to my
cousin.
>> I banished that thing to the corner of
the ceiling after I caught the little
demon getting into my stash of Oreo
drumsticks that had been hidden in the
back of the freezer.
[Music]
>> Let me down.
>> You're staying up there for at least 10
minutes.
>> Don't take my horn.
>> You will get this back when you behave.
Why are you and Care package getting
married at the same time and venue as me
and Saurin? We didn't discuss this.
>> It was Twilight's idea.
Rainbow Dash told me you've been
drinking and are not in the right headsp
space to look after Scootaloo, so I was
worried.
>> Excuse me. I am not drunk.
>> Don't listen to her. She's been drinking
all morning. So, I sense Galoo away
before she starts throwing things like
she always does.
>> Me and my fat pumpkin have just been
arguing. Yes, statistically lesbians
tend to do that.
>> Don't call me a pumpkin.
>> I was calling you that endearingly.
Please go away. I am embarrassed.
>> Hey, me and some of my friends are
turning Spirit Halloween into a wedding
chapel while Celestia is out of town. Do
you want to come renew your vows and
relight the spark that has been lost
between the two of you? When is the
Domino's Pizza going to be here?
>> Is food all you ever think about? What
about my feelings? Does caring about
your feelings reward me with a side of
garlic butter dipping sauce?
>> What time should we go to the spirit
Halloween?
>> Can a [__] get a corn on the cob?
>> Get over here.
>> Lyra and Bon Bon, a little pony told me
one of you hit the other. Is that true?
>> No. Hey, me and some of my friends are
turning Spirit Halloween into a wedding
chapel while Celestia is out of town. Do
you want to come renew your vows and
relight the spark that has been lost
between the two of you?
>> That makes it sound like the spark was
ever there to begin with.
>> Oh my god, you two are herier than I
thought. I was only halfway through
wiping my ass.
>> Well, can you go finish? No, what I have
to say is more important.
>> I doubt it.
>> We are going to kill Applejack. He's
been way too soft on the whole at her
cousin's beating thing. First, Brain,
then her brother, now Apple Bottom.
She's allowed their behavior to go
completely unchecked. Discipline is long
overdue.
>> Okay. Why don't you just kill her gay
cousins, then leave her alone?
>> Cuz I know her personally, and I want to
see the light leave her eyes as I tell
her that the rest of her family is next.
>> Girl, you got to wipe your butt crack.
It literally smells like [__] in here.
>> I've been planning this for 15 whole
minutes. And I realized we are the only
three [__] who are capable of getting
away with it. I have wings which will
let me fly away after the cops are
called. You Twilight are the student of
Princess Celestia, and she wouldn't dare
send you to jail afterwards. And Derpy
can just claim it was an accident due to
her disability. Well, I have to head to
Spirit Halloween since I promised Saurin
and Braburn and Applesplit and Care
Package and Lyra and Bon Bon and
Scootaloo's lesbian ants and Mr. and
Mrs. Cakes that I would help them all
set up their wedding and or help them
renew their vows.
>> That's fine. Me and Rippy can do it by
ourselves. Just don't be in our line of
fire.
>> I don't want to do it either, actually.
>> Never mind then. I can do it myself.
Twilight, can I borrow your butt crack
gun?
>> Absolutely not. You do not have a legal
carry permit.
>> Hey, thanks.
>> Now, I want all of you to be on your
best behavior at Spirit Halloween
tonight.
Yes.
>> Why Spirit Halloween?
>> Cuz that's the only place in town with a
fog machine. Yes, ugly baby sister.
>> So, should we dress up in Halloween
costumes or in gay clothes because it's
a gay wedding? Just dress like you're
going to a normal wedding. Yes. Other
ugly baby.
>> What kind of music will it be playing?
Gay music.
>> Probably some Lady Gaga and Chapel Rome.
Yes.
>> Would it be disrespectful to leave?
>> Oh, that's a good question.
>> You can leave at any time.
>> No, I mean when the music starts. I
don't like Lady Gaga.
>> How the hell can you not like Lady Gaga?
Speak your mind. Granny Smith. When does
the former mistress of one of them burst
in threatening to take her own life?
>> Granny, far as I'm aware, neither of
them have ever had a former mistress.
>> Why are they gay or something?
>> Well, if it isn't the stallion of the
hour,
>> let somebody else shoot him, too. If
he's dead, he can't get married and ruin
the family legacy.
>> [__] I told you not to come here.
Granny Smith has a legal carry permit.
Saurin wanted to come and get her
permission to marry me.
>> Getting up. Granny Smith, stop. Saurin
is rich as hell. If he gives us just a
teensy bit of his Wonderboat money,
we'll be set for life.
>> I don't care about no wonder butts. The
only butt I wonder about is a man's
butt. Cause I'm straight.
>> Twilight, what's this?
>> What's what? Saurin and I picked Spirit
Halloween as our wedding venue two whole
weeks ago. You knew that. What were you
thinking? Inviting all the others here
to host their own events.
>> I just noticed a lot of ponies around
Ponyville were feeling down. And
>> Sugar Daddy Saurin is the one paying to
have it rented out.
>> No, no, stop. A woman is speaking. As
Princess Celestia's prize pupil, it is
my job to keep all ponies feeling happy
and secure while she's away, secure in
safety, and within themselves. Jesus
Christ. All this tells me is I got to
stop trying to help those who are
ungrateful.
>> We don't care. We can't all have our
weddings here. What are we going to do?
Take turns. Bon Bon doesn't even want to
renew her vows with me anymore after the
[__] you pulled.
>> Well, that part isn't really Twilight's
fault.
>> But if there's no event, that means no
guests and no way I'll be able to pay
for the entertainment.
>> Entertainment?
>> Oh my god. Is it the Jonas Brothers?
I don't even know who that [__] is.
>> She's Star Song, a famous pop singer. So
what is she going to sing for us while
my wife eats my ass?
>> Your wife shouldn't be doing that in the
first place. This is a spirit Halloween
where Philly's shop.
>> So my [__] ass husband can't eat mine
either.
>> Show of hooves. Which ponies are so
delusional they genuinely thought they
were going to leave Spirit Halloween
with their ass ate by their partner
today?
Dad,
>> get over here. Get over here now.
>> Mom, Dad, you really came all the way
from Appleissa.
>> Your granny Smith told us you were
getting married, but the [__] didn't
tell us to whom.
>> Does she have huge titties?
>> Daddy, I would like to introduce you to
well, to my other daddy. His name is
Saurin and he's the love of my life.
Even if he's a couple years older than
you,
>> Mom.
>> It's okay. I missed this time. But do
you see what you do to this family? Were
all the childhood beatings from the both
of us not enough for you?
>> So, you are the stallion who releases
his bodily fluids into my son.
>> Actually, it's the other way around. So
Brayburn is a top
good man in that regard at least
>> only because at his age he struggles to
perform properly without his pills.
>> Okay, I'm going out for a smoke and to
take my anger out on your mom by
punching her in the face.
>> Your dad seems really nice. In what way?
I was trying to lie to cheer you up, but
I couldn't think of anything. All that
man has done for me is given me the
worst day of my life.
Honey, where is Brayburn? My brother
Bright Mack and his stupid parabage are
visiting and they want to take Brayburn
with their kids to Chuck-E-Cheese.
>> I'm sitting on him because he was
pissing me off by bedazzling his Bible
again because he's gay.
>> Well, put him in the car. I don't want
my brother to know I'm letting our gross
homo baby be abused again.
Oh, you're here,
>> Simon. Of course I'd be here. The whole
entire Apple family loves Chuck-E-Cheese
almost as much as we love apples.
>> I just thought that after our fight,
you'd stay away out of fear of running
into me again.
>> Real man, fear nothing.
>> You know, I still think about you from
time to time. And that night,
>> Simon, I told you never to talk to me
again.
>> We're at an Apple family gathering. I
would think this is the one place I
should be allowed to talk to you to just
catch up. We are both married with child
now. It's selfexplanatory. We have
nothing to catch up on. Do you ever
regret it being shackled down to this
lifestyle?
>> I hope some pony jabs a knife through
your skull one day. At least I'd be
going out like a badass. You're the type
of pony to off yourself one day when
things get tough. Applejack, where's
your brother and that devil worshipping
son of mine?
>> They are doing what in the ball pit?
Because of that little stunt you pulled
together, I brought you out here to play
football so I can remind you what it
means to be men. Briburn, start running.
Big Mac, take this football and throw it
as hard as you can at Brayburn.
>> Won't that hurt him?
>> Real men only truly feel alive when we
feel pain.
Where are we going? I don't think my mom
and dad would approve of you taking me
somewhere without them knowing.
>> Shut up. Your parents failed you and I
am going to fix their wrongs.
>> What does this thing do? It's a gun. It
lets you kill things. I want one of you
to shoot the other.
>> Why did you shoot me?
>> I only did what I was told. I don't like
gun.
>> Yes, you do. You are a man. Aren't you
shoot him again?
>> How are we going to get home?
>> I don't know. Want to make out?
>> Yeah. and then we can try shoving the
gun up my
long story short, I went home even gayer
that night.
Dad, at traditional weddings, the dad
usually walks the bride down the aisle.
Our wedding already is quite far away
from being traditional. And I know I'm
not a bride, but I'd be nervous walking
out there alone, and I would want
nothing more than for the man who
brought me into this world to walk out
there by my side. You know, after I
passed my jeans into your sexy mother,
who is also my biological sister, I
punched her in the belly every single
day you were in there, hoping that if
the child we'd conceive were a girl,
that my punches would kill it. Or it
were a boy, I would toughen it up. And I
see now that I wish my punches had
killed you. You didn't come out tough at
all. You're a [__] with no balls.
You're no son of mine, and you're sure
as hell no apple. If you go through with
this and give our family name to that
homo wonderbolt out there, I hope you
are ready to rot in horse hell for all
eternity. Goodbye, Rayburn. Or should I
say Gayburn, don't follow us back to
Appaloosa, unless you want a bullet to
your skull. I guess your dad isn't
walking you down the aisle.
>> I never loved him, but a piece of me was
hoping that maybe he loved me. I can't
replace your dad. But if you'll have me,
I will gladly walk you down the aisle so
you don't have to do it alone.
>> Saurin, look. All of Ponyville came
since they heard you and Brayburn are
getting married. Look, Pinky, your weird
ass gray sisters are here, too.
>> Hey, Pinky.
>> Hi there, Mod.
>> I'm surprised you still ride that
fourperson bicycle.
>> Yeah, it's getting harder by the day
since there's only three of us. You
know, it would go a lot of faster if you
would ride it with us sometime. Have you
ever thought about coming home?
>> No.
>> Oh, okay. We heard your friends are
getting married, so we wanted to come
visit.
>> And we also heard they're gay and like
taking it in the pooper. Is that true?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, for the love of Jesus Christ.
>> I guess it makes sense that if any of us
were to make friends with those whipping
the LGBT community,
>> I call them the alphabet mafia. It would
be you, Pinky, since you left the rock
farm to see what the world has to offer.
Back on the farm, all we have to talk to
are rocks.
>> Just so you know, we're sitting in the
back row because I'm violently
homophobic and I don't know what I'll do
if I have to sit within close proximity
to a homosexual.
>> A little congratulations from this clown
to you.
>> Ari knows. Pass on the message to
Brayburn for me too, please. And also
congratulations to Apple Split and Care
Package.
[Music]
Okay, I'm ready to go. Any place you
want to see before we head out? There is
nothing of interest to me around here.
>> Tastes like rotted meat.
[Music]
Hold on. No. No. Stop the wedding.
>> What is this?
>> Cousin Big Mac offered to walk me down
the aisle.
>> We're not doing this. Every pony here
knows what you two used to do in the
Chuck-E-Cheese ball pit. Big Mac, go sit
over there. What are you wearing?
>> I'm dressed as a pumpkin for Halloween.
>> It's not Halloween. It's the beginning
of August.
>> I just thought that since we're in a
spirit Halloween.
>> Look around you, Brayburn. Is literally
any pony else in costume?
>> No.
[Music]
>> As beautiful as a prince.
>> Um, I knew from the moment I met you,
you were the one I'd want to spend my
whole life with.
>> Do you still make Saurin dress up as Big
Mac when you want him to spank you?
Hey yo, Mr. Cakes, I heard you recently
had kids.
>> We sure did. Two healthy twin boys.
>> Girl, that's crazy. I wish you could put
a couple in me, too. Haha. Hey, have you
ever thought of popping those ones in a
furnace and cheating on your wife by
sitting on my face and then going to
Applebee's to share a plate of pasta?
>> Of course not. I'm sure you've seen the
size of her boobies. She's got like two
big mounds on the front of her chest.
>> She might got that cheesecake in the
front, but I've got both cheesecake in
the front and beefcake in the back. And
wouldn't you rather have the best of
both worlds when it's being offered?
>> I'm straight.
>> Oh, no. No. Yeah, I get that. Turning
straight, guys. Gay is kind of my thing.
>> I heard your mom and dad left, but it's
fine. We don't need their blessing, do
we? Not when we have all of Ponyville
here with us now.
Poor
Saurin gives his vows. Would any pony
like to voice their reasons as to why
they think these two ponies should not
be married? Oh, that's why all of
Ponyville came. Hey, Saurin, remember
me? Spitfire, your commander in the
Wonderbolts. What's been going on since
you started dating this cowboy Twink?
You haven't been flying with us. It's
literally been 6 months since you
performed.
>> What can I say? It's hard performing
when my mind wanders home to Brayburn's
unwiped ass cheeks.
>> Okay. Is that like all you're going to
say?
>> Can we wrap this up? It looks like two
more lines are starting to form in the
aisle.
>> Rainbow Dash, please don't do this.
Scuttaloo has always envisioned that she
would be the one to marry you someday,
not some man.
>> My name is Saurin. Oh, I thought you
were Rainbow Dash. You Pegasi all look
the same to me. That's kind of racist.
>> You are also a Pegasus ma'am.
>> Ah, so I am
>> fat [__]
>> Who said that? Which one of you said
that? I know he was one of you.
>> Calm down. They weren't being serious.
>> The hell do you mean they weren't being
serious? If you haven't noticed already,
love, I'm built like a tub of
mayonnaise.
>> I have to go give my cousin a few words,
too.
>> Just a few more step forward and your
ass is grass.
>> Hey, has any pony seen where Apple split
and care package went off to?
>> Now, how did you possibly get a whole
entire gummy worm stuck between your
teeth?
>> Does it matter? It's out now. Here. I
just bought a new toothbrush, but you
can have it. In fact, how about I brush
for you?
>> I can do it myself.
>> Proper brushing is important, and I
believe I am far better at brushing than
you are.
[Laughter]
There's some pony up on the shelves.
>> I told you all it's the former mistress
here to enact her petty revenge.
>> Twilight Blast.
>> Fluttershy, you're really here. I
thought you were trolling. Damn you,
crazy girl.
>> What's going on here?
>> Me and Saurin are getting married. Okay,
you two are being hung. Every pony out
to the Ponyville Square.
>> Wait, if you're going to hang them, then
you have to hang me, too, cuz I'm the
one who made their wedding cake from
scratch.
>> And I handtailored their suits. You will
not ruin this promotional endeavor for
me.
>> I will stand by Brain. But even if they
like taking it up the ass,
>> they're not the only ones. Me and Care
package do too. This fat [__] and I
are here to renew our vows because our
love for each other is more powerful
than your hatred for gay ponies.
>> What we're saying is if you're going to
hang Brayurn and Saurin, then you have
to hang all of us because every pony in
this room played a part.
>> Okay,
I have no problem hanging like 30 of you
when there's 300 other ponies who live
in Pony Bell.
>> You don't have to hang me, Celestia. In
fact, I was the only one who followed
your rules while you were out of town.
>> I don't even know who you are.
>> Luna, go start constructing that big
wooden thing we hang ponies with.
>> You mean the public gallows?
>> Sick name? Is that what it's called?
I've been calling it the bye-bye
balcony.
>> Any last words?
>> I have only ever been celest
crashed through Pinkie Pie's house.
Okay, drop them.
>> I'm not about to let Celestia get in the
last hit on you, Applejack. This will be
my total and absolute victory.
>> Should I missed
>> every pony run?
>> Fluttershy.
>> Oh, hey, Twilight.
>> You saved our lives.
>> I knew you were always on our side. I
just knew it.
>> You know what? Yeah. Yeah, I did. I
saved the day. Fluttershy finally saved
the day. Oh gosh, girls. This might just
be the best day ever. So much so I could
[__]
[Music]
>> You are
by my side.
[Music]
Summer days will turn cold.
All the leaves fade to gold.
The season may change,
but one thing remains.
You are always by my side.
You hold me high up and see me through
lows.
When I need someone,
I know where to go.
In my darkest times,
you're the light that I follow.
You are always by my side.
Days may pass into years.
Things we know disappear.
We lose and we gain.
But one thing remains.
You are
by my side.
You hold me high up and see me through
lows.
When I need,
I know where to go.
In my darkest hours,
you're the light that I follow.
You are
by my side.
You were there to help me along.
You give me love that makes me feel
strong.
You let me know just where I feel.
You are
by
[Music]
Over
the edge. Feel like I'm floating through
the air.
The pain I felt is paid for. All is said
and done.
Oh,
I am restricted, fixed upon the web. I
need to kick the habit that my mind is
breathing in.
Break I've got break I've got.
Spent all my life holding all of it
closely.
I played it in a sense. A feel of
discontent. I'm finally facing it all.
Fearless.
Feel it
burning the bridge that keeps us.
I'm here and I'm feeling
fearless.
Exaggerated. That's what you assume.
The stories over now I must conclude.
Eyes
watching where I step. Still hanging in
the balance. Not the life I want to
live. I won't take it all. Standing
tall. You wait the first.
Oh,
break out. I've got to see. Break out.
I've got to see. Spend all my life
holding it all closely.
I'm playing it in the field of
discontent. I'm finally facing it all.
Fearless.
Feelingless. Feel
it.
[Applause]
[Music]